hi welcome back to our online retreat
the wheel of life retreat previous
machine image online the typical
Association and I'd like to welcome
shopping yeah a cheapo previous thoughts
well the Betty the other stern a bleep
you I didn't see working so we're on
section II mean our small village in the
name of this session is what it's like
to live in the part in as one yet was a
Nitish toes not cheating Barbra
and the picture we're using for this
class in covering misfortune lettuce
onion tail is a burnt black tree trunk
the shore miss Duvall's got a fish on a
deal
and we'll explain more you might
distinguish a button
- so I think at first most of us know
the word Pardo I do move up arrow
buttons to Anna's knives not genius
level Barba apartments are in between
bar as much a traditional amparo means
the state in between in Bordeaux of the
Chad premiere Edition SSI Union it means
the state between after you die I'll
tell you are we it has not yet premiere
edition assist a an image the post of
Asha Smith endo pyridinium so we're
continuing with this idea of how lousy
is life attacking prodigy idea Tom
Carper Shuji her shop and we have
trouble all through our life see we mean
probably any trouble or through Virginia
Nash's reason
and then also again in the party we have
the same trumpet on taxes no bargain sto
mm so
talk about what it's like to be in the
part that's divided to forgive at him
cook envoys and hundreds of barber and
I'm gonna read from the Tibetan I hope
you'll follow that yeah at CBS comedy is
for postulate is that you get skin I
know not all of you want to learn to bed
yes then you see it was quite a position
to be asking but I'm trying to put a
seed in your mind
yeah probably misses a mushroom to read
this very holy books so which is that
each institution leaked ningún to read
the original sheet I said it you know it
puts a very deep-seated if I said
watching global casino wash Amamiya and
we will meet again in the next my spine
straight insist no ops clearly she
reason to study translation to be the
check today what's missing so I'm
planting does actually a plate save it
is enough me Puccini Pato do look me now
the second part of this discussion that
I chest a table Sardinia how is it that
we go into the park seduction
imperialism's Barbour and what happens
in the past what iswhat is Barden she
said gotta she see she see is a special
expression she stood us up in a Virginia
there are four kinds of zippers so she's
what she did
he that she's she's under is new in this
case C means kind of being welcome Fuji
see Anna Chad booth
Bhatia
and TC means the person or the being at
the time of day she said as much every
week
ELISA she stroked my face meeting so she
see God Borgata means ending she see doc
Bangkok has matured Canyon so to see
Garba means you know the person is dying
on their Hospital attack she said God
Posner said she like a dreamer I have no
punishment question the person is dying
and then tune young do I become Murad is
a team joonyoung do means at the same as
much at all just a Amamiya someday to
mention do means in the old days when
they wave food for example they will use
a scale it doesn't change of star every
Minocqua definitely do premier sports
very sisterly material come in and you
know as this plate comes down it comes
out not a little cup of sky 7 News this
plate goes oh god I don't open you might
sell here so they say the appearance
Vikon garage to read that you have Italy
made at the time of my name's mutant
your outer passion is needed it starts
to finish that is she said and at the
same time another appearance starts to
come in
if todo momento goodness needn't should
not leave letter and you take the
appearance of the person you will bring
you might even ears mr. lovak of Bardo
so your your face your body start to
chill it so why should you only Chennai
admin user the past face and body you
had when you were dying it's so it's
yogacara was Balkan devil nyalam is
replaced by the face and the body that
you're going to have it zooming eternal
it so it's yellow color of ability made
partner
and that Bardo person's appearance he
will ania at of a barber Chihuahua
here it says mon Dieu kissy bicep
chanting it matches the appearance of
the person before is this that business
notice that V Elstad the National
videociao a condo ethic and this is a
very confusing idea watching is up with
an idea
no you lose it any prying open tomorrow
oh when I come down your mirror and I go
to the bargain my appearance will be the
appearance of the person before village
gotcha like that huh
but it means the appearance of the
person before your next as much as
venetian official record of our she's
clearly she's nursing
so that means the parents are going to
have in your next actually does not
Japanese need Qatar elaborate I did wash
is clear the she reason so the
appearance that you take on in the party
that Venetian you need cover have a
plenty myself pardon
it's related to who you are going to be
after you come out of the gym gym the
Buddha to post liver her this bottle so
here it says K what she may look
ichi-chan do you take on a body of the
that is related to the body you're going
to have when you come out of it has
discovery sister fabricated tilaka
terrestrials nice young cattle Ava's
bullet could've avoided his barber when
Duke is zipper Shepparton
and here he clarifies he says by the way
when the scripture says that being at
the time is this insertion is incorrect
article so covered FP sonic what it's
just war aiming in door
it means the pin you're going to pay for
a whole lifetime before you die in the
next image reduces to Ekaterinburg
Buddhism so this prayer dish among
rotisserie reason
Kartik he shambled a samba captain
numbered dung Dziedzic gender your
passion so some people say nectarine
losing covariant the dead person
Mitchell Anya looks like how they in the
barter they looked like the person they
used bar double is it objection
cattleman go then part Ola dead do pay
and they sit in the park she likes you
do Pardo and you can send them messages
and they will reply you know with even
written even more sterilized Museveni on
a twisted form - appeasement of
subterranean and in America we have some
if America knows he sneaking a donkey
and they will you go to them you say I
want to talk to my father who died the
most affected name is Katja how'd you
convince the other with my motion o
muhammad saw then they kind of have
trick way to write letters and they say
unique our base hit responsible episode
vamp is more a OS mutt recon mission to
date a small subterranean here says
there are face discoveries and if cfl
sugar so he says be careful of this like
fortune it happens very Buddhist
erogenous a Tomica document some of them
just making my new trees new process
they're about avoiding you they are
making fake letters from your knees they
eventually piss mouthwash commercial
thinker but you you can you can see a
part of being and you can talk to them
it's but over more visitors to a bar
Deepika very immediately sees Nawaz
Muslim then darling
Tony Kyung says it's possible you could
see your relative in the bottle it is
possible is governance of amore to visit
several snick of bartology sitting about
muslim and it's also possible that
someone who looks like your relative in
the borough is not really your relative
you know doc she was Mishnah touched
include the bajalia Navarro sneak of
Barden asam didn't Eve let martial arts
income pardon me my inky symbols so soon
a jig temp help a lure check this is a
kind of spirit being a slave or deduce
which is paw its kind of ghost say what
are the breed in young and they like to
take the appearance of your relative
patron I had to bring my teeth washed a
little cynical and they trick any of
money class J milla milla means a
malaria Jaime Lemieux has matured Nalepa
a very very famous meditator from OSHA
anemone they mastered me get that psycho
did not know that and they there's
a story in his hundred thousand years
thorium's thought in British person
which is in Tibetan is Gorger boom which
means hundred thousand songs so she
becomes mushy goo boo me as much as
soybean piece each patient then there's
a story there about how he met someone's
father from the bottom yesterday Tomo
constancy water Elsa is Bardo and he
guided your no problem
and apparently there was also some ghost
in the story who was imitating that
Ibaka with this terrible Nicky please
recovery pod Raja mashallah echo and I'd
be interested if any of you guys
listening you could read those hundred
thousand songs of millet in noble win
seriousness immobility revision and
liske down or accompanying garma CC the
name he translated a hundred thousand is
a mistake Dokic Imperial news Vanya stop
this is she made a mistranslation owns
the only privately pyramid in the tire
so for example silver doesn't mean a
hundred thousand bucks
Tecna premiers subbu me as much as
thought this is Nick it just means a
collection the process Michele
colleagues evening but generally the
translation I think is not so bad and
maybe maybe some of you guys can find a
story telling Peter what Natasha bloke
who has mostly nectaries vastly better
smoke good night a historian
it's not a hundred thousand stories but
it's a lot and I I don't have time to
read the whole thing but you guys kept
Tommy so did she study Nam noggin in
your image that should know very better
mostly the pitched at Cana part Oh
anyone but cool summer so part of being
really does have eyes ears nose
everything attacks which is nobody sees
me meet gloves are whoosh and also if
stuff complected moisture Europe are
means a business they have the ability
to they have special and you sure you
passed my children exist I saw women
Thailand I can understand our language
premiere among pretty much see is a key
and they have the truth the term means
they can do miracle isn't it is - tool
so true was not shared anymore example
they can walk through walls a mere
animal bodies question they can travel
millions of miles you know animal three
machines is Emilio only the million
meals at chess at Buddhism says that's
how new planets are populated virginica
body system that exists allowed to
Norway plan yet this what a clue
depressed riveted mirror
so worlds are countless beginningless
and you know people move from one to
another one a million miles away in
popular memory beaches in when you can
touch a little deeper in Michelle's
eternal dragoons Emilio in the mill
insulator then that ability to walk
through walls
it was madness to hadith question it's
very interesting if if the wall is is
part of a temple yes mr. Nye you've led
chest you Kurama or a holy place like I
know but guy illicit or mr. premier
about Gaia they when they hit that wall
they cannot they cannot go through
anywhere in the world they can walk
through accept our good enemies to God
it seemed to animo good practice kasnia
Dubois jenna maroney Martinez cause
description thank you so some wall
that's connected to a holiday Saxony
Christina I said she succeeded mr. it
was stopped
Anika standard and the skin at the back
of a woman's Hoosier zag knee chest
Asian school trouble decoration come on
Mitaka means the chaos feel it doesn't
shed any Nemo good parenting the gets
every time just revive and that's where
many of them are even abdominal is nice
better - lesson next pub uncle Rinpoche
describes the physical appearance of
this piece lollipop on can push a piece
with veneers Mysterio suggests
so we said they take on the appearance
that corresponds to their next attack
nagoba readers tiny primitive eats at a
sushi Dushi margin that doesn't mean if
they're going to be reborn as a very
tall guy that during the bottle they
look like a very tall guy that's not a
thing is not tasty like sobriety Peter I
did the washing mystic apartment of a
prima Barb and ugly the question was
occupy
it means what kind of rebirth they're
going to take it does not shed Pocoyo
genius dress up Lynette you can tell it
from the appearance in the part where
the magis - dyspnea movie doe Pardo so
he gives here some examples psycho
musician provided me asking you dr.
pepper slaw me that's maybe a premium
person in the house other person who
becomes a hungry Saturdays tonight the
government local person who is going to
become a catalyst annotation one person
who is going to be a pleasure of being
in the desire like a pair of boots which
is formidable steps here is Lonnie and a
human each illogical ok day what did
they look like in the canyon rim may rim
shin means if we start one by one to
tell you from the bottom meaning from
the hell really medium she has no chance
to use simulation pop erotica Sneasel
tells my chances here at Alden to meet
Sigma Mensa people in the bottle who are
going to be reborn into the hell realms
they look their body looks like the
stump of a burnt tree it has no chance
Lou give Bardo cattle several periods of
ceará odd if silverglade pings gary
of shows ever
if you're going to be born as a hungry
cord yes the varieties go on and go home
your body looks like water if you're
going to be born as an animal you see
what I did you want them to are your
body looks like smoke
do I I should tell a bug is it coming
depends love me if you're going to be a
pleasure being or human in the design
room yes the visibility's bit so just
one more diversity each lever comes here
Jelani search on the tablet and doctor
you have a body that looks like very
fine gold look up watching her oceans
all sue come be part o Coppola if you're
going to be born into the form rel maybe
you did those formalities yes the
bride's relatives fee reform orbit video
let's remedy that Syriana your body will
be like shining white color I should
tell a boutique oxy I should be less
submit the Kiana part of me but if
you're going to be born into the
formless no service varieties ready it's
very beautiful there is no pot and
Daniel Barden because you're not going
to have a promise to ask me Buddha job
so it's interesting if you if you die if
I die here sitting here you think
seriously I'm gonna see these this and I
will go immediately into my mental Jenny
million a pop adduced value mentality
all right Thomas D okay and that's where
the formless realm is a vodka general
its abyss formula at @anjghie young
Meera
but otherwise Oh was that long kind of
the purpose of the part of the sale barn
Oh is to travel from the place you die
to the place you're going to be at the
British Astor it is mr. get woman mr.
Davis dress tragedy it could be one
never much better than the other it
could be millions of it mean only me and
it takes two seconds I never did not
cover diamond okay the next paragraph
says McGeoch a paper seen me serigraphy
Alicia party means again she means the
person par means in the puddles of Parsi
means the person in the bottle I bet she
has my children borrows my change bar
the bottom of bar see as I change like
generally speaking they were not a very
nice person their home you think what if
they're only for unborn you are so much
alike I'm so sorry to do surgeries say
mama knocked Enomoto they look like kind
of darkness the only person in not to
and that's their pit they look they look
like dark bloody finished Evita unbeliev
cut thumbnail like that you're not that
gay a chip a Parsi knee but the part of
a person who was a good person they're
Hollow no party check opal hanno some
Shivaji number copper means they look
like like whites as I said anybody that
can be a shock Todd and chipper
Seminole they look like white moonlight
at night I Newburgh lead car Billy
lonely sea urchin parted say means well
how long do these things live bar the
waiter said as much a dog among young
there's many many different scriptures
say different things yes oceanography
sunny category at reservation
most of those scriptures are inquisitive
design in New Guinea
there's one in particular called they
translate has Tibetan Book of the bad
news news news vials of chef masti
vampiric activist Cunningham your tongue
and in the traditional some couple who
is very very strict I did some Copic a
trio change in strong got nice text time
of treaty attestation come
he says the original of that poem gotta
study you know and he continued is this
word here it's they call fake it's
fairly so there's Louis poison so party
oka at the fake yeah it's just not
correct it's a person you private now so
I they would the truth this tradition so
coppers tradition would say you know
that book is not correct about the part
by the movie that I did sit and eat some
carbs cause alabaster Technica pardon
Irina culture shock dentition but most
of the great books really cute new
team-mates or shark Hinda it says that
part of being always lived for seven
days so she's Lombardo sick - you've
seen me cannot live for more than I mean
I'm over Jetboil a seemingly there is a
funny debate / bunker says I wonder
which kind of day they're talking the
Tim is above ninja bottlecutter Baba
Yaga very interesting come near me
because a day in the health or a day for
the pleasure beings can be thousand
years but I mostly DHing but Dean
yes we just found the words they're
mostly this is shall I just keep
yep
and he says the chima to shock it means
shock means one day and night 24 hours
yonder means my opinion start ending in
which it was purchased seven days of
where you're going you know the toaster
at the same native open again you become
salvia yes absolutely
sharp but traditionally in in in the
Buddhist monastery for example no trade
its own of the disco monastery a
no-brainer we count Seven Fishes times
seemed me and we start from the day that
the person died even as you know much
ascent yeah come - like a corner so if
they died at one minute to midnight on
Tuesday I can yes yeah on owners admin
to dope all loony love tonic
one minute before midnight on two things
not know me not the dope on 11 identity
said David not sure still we can't
digest number one when we count seven
astronomy sheet I'm at the genome are
imagine contaminated indeed send me and
I had an opportunity on a long plane
flight once Yemeni below us a nice talk
to my own teacher Nadia in Peru tiaras
Guevara was the same Chisholm who again
was a disciple of pop uncle PJ and pop
uncle Rinpoche's heart disciple tutoring
portable Cheney compa bunkie Rinpoche
rich angry but reconciliation which is
the Pamunkey repulsion and I asked I
asked him many questions about this but
oh yes Bradshaw is that all I'm not
gonna process for beating by and he gave
me some great answers beyond downing yes
good good grass and I put all of those
into a kind of a question and answer
people yeah but me still see this piece
of come upon a sofa together and we're
gonna offer it on this podcast you
mister but I'm stupid logic so this
piece of Kavala and podcast there'll be
a link that you can click on and with so
covered almost images you can go to that
explanation by mighty pretty thick at
the mob is Nino
cheater shark duner she then they would
die after seven young men kissing me
then either they go to the life they're
supposed to go to or they come back to
another bottle for seven months the
terminally possession suggests if
Catherine does natively bruschetta
Dragoon barber is shown as in gay or
less any mention so let's say they
they're in the part of her tender
post-money Barbie Sydney after the first
seven days they would appear OC meet me
a new emerald they will come back to
that was Rachelle so that the Bardo for
three Martian Audrina then they die and
become whatever they're supposed to
monument so he calls it here he has a
funny name he calls she - he means
epsilon divided this day is about
niceness violence while teach English
administer its part minute a mystic I'm
Minnie smears Bardo every seven deadly
sins me and Kimmy money I'd say and if
they don't find the rebirth that are
supposed to have healing you my dude
period are Dina Cutrone internal boots
landing keep our data chichi Rachel the
great books say Nicky Nicko by dad and
for example the epidemic OSHA which is
one of the greatest books of duties in
the premiere abhidharma Koscheck
attorney blessedness village ethnic
Buddhism oh and if you're really
interested about the part of yes we
didn't research this bargain
you should read Stanley's translation at
their house either Pritchett that very
water Biederman Stanley and that's
completely colonization of revenue it's
about almost two thousand it's a
question via this Julian and that's a
better source to read than than the
Tibetan Book of the Dead which has many
false fees Ethel Bush Lee is touched
English Tina tchen teabiscuit
Myrtle cattery here Carter is no
governance the other landing depart a
torch each over chasin those great books
say you will have maximum 7 min
death in Sevilla kick knee coverage to
was good at maximum seen me rocket army
got it
so you must take your rebirth within
forty nine take a mobile Samba - no
planet paradeen if teaching is Erica
deleted me counting the day of the death
as the first dance music p.m. that's why
we do traditionally we do those Cheung
Chau prayers what she would read its own
the media limited chunk chocolately
reminding grandpa after all the good
things he asked about chef Cara she'll
do large stones deal traditionally we do
those pears on the seventh day after
death counting the death day as the
first lady phone a mr. Sharma team
illegally sigmoid in process mears's she
tied in smear tip pyramid young and then
again on the forty nine is it a normal
sort of D repeating because within
within that time period almost if the
genius of a video the very meaning they
must they must go I need dollars reason
and they must the seed must be activated
for that there's no bit severan on the
other side it's not activated it must
open it's negative you don't know
there's not a scripted let's say the
shooters
yeah it's activated as they died or not
from the past okay severe a second uh a
numerous cross the reason their last
their last awareness of that if poss
Linnaeus has none of those reasoning and
then it actually opens at the end of on
the 40 G scale provides of concern
bottle and they are born into them
Daniel earth that's obvious reason now
we didn't learn these things in school
or in University Princeton doesn't have
a course on Bartle it's just when you
see China TV ships call University of
Princeton in yet cool so Varga but
everyone has to die - no minute everyone
goes through this totally para college
it is etem Bardo and it's important to
study yet the VARs needs a chat
and it's important to learn marginal
chips it there's a joke in the mothers
sugar if you know you're going on it
like I used to go there to debate yes it
was not justice varieties occupations to
browse it in the D button for suggestion
I remember on the day I was coming back
to America I would debate in the morning
and then I had run to the airport and
come back
yep Amish the toadying on the day I have
to leave the monastery to come back to
America there was a shelf I was still
debated by Marroquin Buddha Patil to
trauma Pitamber that we report back as
routine and I remember the monkeys to
ask me what you know
you're gonna leave today upon yogic mana
is brushed aluminum this brush through
your history Depeche Mode Prevage the
bottle over your suitcase prostate you
gotta switch madam so we're all gonna
die so much sell me on it might be busy
one you do your suitcase right off just
watch modern study the bachata bottle we
don't know if we're gonna enjoy the
money or the family we have next week
when is damn would you watch that
feeding chimera nauseous immunization
easier and when is nambudiri massages
this but sooner or later we have to go
to the war on Aleppo stahma - nearby -
Barba so let's pack our suitcases I buy
tobacco chew madam let's get ready wait
I don't see any more okay see you in the
next online session which is number nine
crucial we didn't substitution once they
see no more David and thank you for
taking my Steven pyramid that pyramids
shopping